Safe And Sound
安然无恙
歌手：Taylor Swift Ft.The Civil Wars
压制:随Feng
I remember tears streaming down your face,when I said I'll never let you go
我曾记泪水流过你的面庞 当我说我不会让你离开的时候
When all those shadows almost killed your light
当暗影几乎抹杀了你的光芒
I remember,you said,don't leave me here alone.
我曾记你说“别留下我孤单一人”
But all that's gone and dead and past, tonight
但就在今晚 所有的一切、死亡的威胁都会过去
Just close your eyes
闭上你的双眼吧
The sun is going down
日沉西山
You'll be alright
你会安然无恙
No one can hurt you now
此刻没人能再把你伤害
Come morning light
黎明就要来到
You and I'll be safe and sound
你我会安然无恙
Don't you dare look out your window, darling,everything's on fire
吾爱 别不敢看向窗外 一切都在燃烧
The war outside our door keeps raging on
战争在外面肆虐
Hold on to this lullaby
继续哼唱你的摇篮曲吧
Even when the music's gone
即便音乐已经远去
Just close your eyes
闭上你的双眼吧
The sun is going down
日沉西山
You'll be alright
你会安然无恙
No one can hurt you now
此刻没人能再把你伤害
Come morning light
黎明就要来到
You and I'll be safe and sound
你我会安然无恙
Just close your eyes
闭上你的双眼吧
You'll be alright
你会安然无恙
Come morning light
黎明就要来到
You and I'll be safe and sound
你我会安然无恙
压制:随Feng